

# Profile

I am a developer with over 5 years of official experience with software development, and 3 years of game development. Most recent work of mine is the Android app for Croatia's largest classified ad website called Njuskalo, which I have worked on for more than 3 years.

My latest success is developing a photo recognition feature that recognizes objects on the photos, where AI analyses the photo and matches them with their belonging categories. If the AI has chosen the wrong category, the user can easily improve the AI by presenting the correct category while making the AI better and smarter.

I have experience working alone and in teams, I know how to communicate with any members of a development team. I have used a wide range of version control and ticket tracking software, and therefore I know how to structure goals to meet deadlines.

I am consistent and very effective when it comes to my work, and I have the necessary skills for the job.

# Employment History

#### Co-Founder at quasiStudio, Zagreb

October 2018 - Present

www.quasi.studio / a modern game development & design studio where we're looking to create memorable digital experiences, games, and have fun along the way.

#### Android Developer at Undabot, Zagreb

September 2015 - February 2019

www.undabot.com / While working at Undabot. I had the opportunity to work on Njuskalo. A leading classifieds Android and iOS app in Croatia, handling over 300,000 ads every month. App currently has more than 640.000 downloads, that is 6x more users than any other similar apps in the area.

# Co-Founder at Kabattle LLC, Oklahoma City

January 2015 - February 2016

a game development studio where we focused on the creation of hyper-casual mobile games

## Education

Mechanical Engineering, Industrijsko-Obrtnička Škola, Slavonski Brod September 2012 – July 2015

#### **Details**

Mirka Turčinovića 9, Slavonski Brod, 35000, Croatia, +385915040139 rstanic12@gmail.com

#### Links

GitHub LinkedIn QuasiStudio

## **Skills**

C/C++

C# Java

Kotlin

Dart

Flutter

Retrofit

RxJava

Butterknife

Git

Unity

Unreal Engine 4

## Languages

English

Croatian